[laughing]
[laughing]
What's with you? Not there, come on!
What's with you? Not there, come on!
Come on, we always do that.
Come on, we always do that.
[muffled chatter]
[muffled chatter]
It's okay, I'll take care of you.
It's okay, I'll take care of you.
Come on! Let's do it later!
Come on! Let's do it later!
- I know where you're ticklish. - Not there!
- I know where you're ticklish. - Not there!
Ramon!
Ramon!
Come on!
Ayuh!
[muffled chatter]
[muffled chatter]
I'm close!
I'm close!
It's so early, why are you in a rush?
It's so early, why are you in a rush?
Babe!
Babe!
- You forgot your ID. - I know right?
- You forgot your ID. - I know right?
- Hey, you better behave. - Babe!
- Hey, you better behave. - Babe!
Babe.
Babe.
Come home early, okay?
Come home early, okay?
Taho...
Taho...
- Hi! - Oh, why are you late?
- Hi! - Oh, why are you late?
Got stuck in traffic.
Got stuck in traffic.
But don't worry, I'm here now.
But don't worry, I'm here now.
Come in.
Come in.
[muffled chattering]
[muffled chattering]
Not there, it tickles!
Not there, it tickles!
Stop it!
Hentikan!
Shit...
Shit...
Shit!
Shit!
- Does it feel good? - So much!
- Does it feel good? - So much!
Shit!
Shit!
So good!
So good!
Oh shit!
Oh shit!
It feels so good!
It feels so good!
Really?
Betul ke?
That felt so good...
That felt so good...
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot, isn't it?
But it's cloudy.
But it's cloudy.
You're right.
You're right.
Are you the new tenant?
Are you the new tenant?
Yeah, I moved in just last week.
Yeah, I moved in just last week.
It's quiet here every Sunday.
It's quiet here every Sunday.
The tenants head home to their provinces.
The tenants head home to their provinces.
It's okay. I like it better when it's quiet.
It's okay. I like it better when it's quiet.
Me too.
Me too.
Alright, well, I'll go ahead.
Alright, well, I'll go ahead.
- Good evening. - Good evening!
- Good evening. - Good evening!
Excuse me!
Excuse me!
Is there someone inside?
Is there someone inside?
Oh! There's no one there.
Oh! There's no one there.
She left to go to Cavite.
She left to go to Cavite.
Oh, I was hoping to get my lights fixed.
Oh, I was hoping to get my lights fixed.
The bulb burned out.
The bulb burned out.
Where is it? I'll check.
Where is it? I'll check.
Okay, if you can do it.
Okay, if you can do it.
Thank you.
terima kasih.
Do you have an extra bulb?
Do you have an extra bulb?
Yeah, wait, I have one.
Yeah, wait, I have one.
Here.
Di sini.
There. It's okay now.
There. It's okay now.
Wow. Thank you.
Wow. Thank you.
I thought I was going to eat in total darkness.
I thought I was going to eat in total darkness.
It's okay if you eat in the dark.
It's okay if you eat in the dark.
It's exciting.
It's exciting.
I haven't tried it yet.
I haven't tried it yet.
Try it next time.
Try it next time.
I'll go now.
I'll go now.
Thank you.
terima kasih.
I'll probably do double duty tonight.
I'll probably do double duty tonight.
Okay. Take care.
Okay. Take care.
Could you please close the door for me?
Could you please close the door for me?
Yeah, I'll handle it.
Yeah, I'll handle it.
Okay.
Okay.
You're just on time, she just left.
You're just on time, she just left.
You're so beautiful.
You're so beautiful.
Sit down.
Duduklah.
Thank you.
terima kasih.
How are you?
How are you?
I'm doing good. You?
I'm doing good. You?
I'm fine too.
I'm fine too.
I prepared something for you.
I prepared something for you.
- Wow. - Because you're special.
- Wow. - Because you're special.
You're really prepared, huh?
You're really prepared, huh?
Of course, anything for you!
Of course, anything for you!
I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I'll do it myself.
I'll do it myself.
Okay.
Okay.
You missed me, didn't you?
You missed me, didn't you?
- I missed this. - Really?
- I missed this. - Really?
Mhm!
Mhm!
Shit. So good!
Shit. So good!
See? I told you!
See? I told you!
- You're right. - Yeah!
- You're right. - Yeah!
- You're so sexy! - Hey!
- You're so sexy! - Hey!
So good.
So good.
Thank you.
terima kasih.
Take care.
Jaga diri.
You too.
You too.
I enjoyed.
I enjoyed.
Hi.
Hai.
You're the new tenant?
You're the new tenant?
Yes.
ya.
- I'm Mara, by the way. - Lea.
- I'm Mara, by the way. - Lea.
You're quiet, aren't you?
You're quiet, aren't you?
That's how I am.
That's how I am.
I don't have anyone to talk to.
I don't have anyone to talk to.
Is he your husband?
Is he your husband?
Partner.
Partner.
We've been together for eight years, not yet married.
We've been together for eight years, not yet married.
He doesn't want to propose yet.
He doesn't want to propose yet.
He's not here?
He's not here?
He has work. Sometimes he isn't here during the evening.
Dia ada kerja. Kadang-kadang dia tiada di sini pada waktu petang.
Have you been living here for long?
Adakah anda telah lama tinggal di sini?
About two years.
Lebih kurang dua tahun.
Okay.
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
Selamat berkenalan.
Nice to meet you, Lea.
Gembira berkenalan dengan awak, Lea.
You're up early.
Awak bangun awal.
I haven't slept yet.
Saya belum tidur lagi.
What's that?
Apa itu?
Insomnia?
Insomnia?
Do you need help?
Adakah anda memerlukan bantuan?
I'm fine.
saya sihat.
Thanks.
Terima kasih.
You're welcome.
Anda dialu-alukan.
What's your perfume?
Apa minyak wangi awak?
That's just my shampoo.
Itu hanya syampu saya.
It smells good.
Baunya sedap.
What's your name, by the way?
Siapa nama awak, by the way?
Lea.
Itu sahaja.
Okay. I'll go inside.
Okay. Saya akan masuk ke dalam.
Hello!
hello!
Do you know how to fix a sink?
Adakah anda tahu bagaimana untuk membaiki sinki?
Why? What's wrong?
kenapa? apa salahnya
It's leaking.
Ia bocor.
Let's go check it out.
Mari kita pergi menyemaknya.
Come on. Let's go inside.
Ayuh. Jom masuk dalam.
- Where is it? - There.
- Di mana ia? - Di sana.
Oh, here it is.
Oh, ini dia.
Seems like the valve is loose.
Nampaknya injap longgar.
Do you have a wrench?
Adakah anda mempunyai sepana?
I don't have one.
Saya tidak mempunyai satu.
Let me do this...
Biar saya buat ini...
The pressure's a bit weak.
Tekanannya agak lemah.
I'm going to borrow a wrench.
Saya akan meminjam sepana.
Thank you so much.
Terima kasih banyak-banyak.
Are you always this quiet?
Adakah anda selalu senyap ini?
I just don't know what to say.
Cuma saya tak tahu nak cakap apa.
What? Why?
apa? kenapa?
Nothing.
tiada apa.
So good!
sangat bagus!
You can't sleep?
Anda tidak boleh tidur?
I can't.
saya tak boleh.
What about you?
Bagaimana dengan awak?
Trying to.
Berusaha untuk.
Do you love her?
Adakah anda mencintainya?
It's complicated.
Ia rumit.
Are you just trying to make me feel better?
Adakah anda hanya cuba membuat saya berasa lebih baik?
No.
Tidak.
That's the truth.
Itulah kebenarannya.
Then why are you here?
Jadi kenapa awak ada di sini?
I don't know.
saya tak tahu.
Okay.
Okay.
I don't really care anyways.
Saya tak kisah sangat pun.
No goodbye kiss?
Tiada ciuman selamat tinggal?
Take care.
Jaga diri.
I'm close... I'm close!
Saya dekat... saya dekat!
Miss me?
rindu saya?
Yes.
ya.
Just relax.
Rileks sahaja.
Want to explore something?
Ingin meneroka sesuatu?
I love you.
saya sayang awak.
Louder!
Lebih kuat!
Okay, fine.
Okay, baiklah.
Because of that, here's your reward.
Kerana itu, inilah ganjaran anda.
Harder!
Lebih keras!
You feel so good...
Anda berasa sangat baik...
I'm close! I'm so close!
saya dekat! Saya sangat dekat!
I didn't see you last night.
Saya tak jumpa awak semalam.
I was reviewing.
Saya sedang mengulangkaji.
Good girl.
perempuan baik.
Don't! Someone might see.
jangan! Seseorang mungkin melihat.
You're too paranoid.
Awak terlalu paranoid.
You seem busy lately.
Anda kelihatan sibuk kebelakangan ini.
Yes.
ya.
Busy with work.
Sibuk dengan kerja.
You know how it is.
Anda tahu bagaimana keadaannya.
Oh, you're working.
Oh, awak sedang bekerja.
Okay. I'll go ahead.
Okay. Saya akan pergi ke hadapan.
Morning!
Pagi!
Hey. I have a question for you.
Hei. Saya ada soalan untuk awak.
What is it?
Apa itu?
Do you know the feeling that there's something wrong?
Adakah anda tahu perasaan bahawa ada sesuatu yang tidak kena?
But you don't know why.
Tetapi anda tidak tahu mengapa.
What do you mean?
apa maksud awak?
Like there's something going on with Ramon.
Seperti ada sesuatu yang berlaku dengan Ramon.
Last night, when I got home, he was already asleep.
Semalam, sampai rumah, dia sudah pun tidur.
But the bed smelled like a woman's shampoo.
Tetapi katil itu berbau seperti syampu wanita.
And...
Dan...
Look.
Tengok.
I saw this on the table.
Saya melihat ini di atas meja.
Whose is that?
Itu milik siapa?
I don't know.
saya tak tahu.
It's not mine.
Ia bukan milik saya.
You're really quiet, huh?
Awak senyap betul ke?
Sorry. I don't know what to say.
Maaf. Tak tahu nak cakap apa.
Anyway, I'm sorry for inconveniencing you.
Bagaimanapun, saya minta maaf kerana menyusahkan anda.
Shit!
sial!
Why?
kenapa?
What do you think of me?
Apa pendapat awak tentang saya?
An idiot?
Bodoh?
I read all of it, Ramon!
Saya membaca semuanya, Ramon!
All your messages!
Semua mesej anda!
You even took pictures!
Anda juga mengambil gambar!
You didn't even bother deleting them, huh?
Anda tidak bersusah payah memadamnya, ya?
You didn't even think about me?
Awak tak fikirkan saya pun?
You know, I'm so tired from working so many shifts.
Anda tahu, saya sangat letih kerana bekerja banyak syif.
You didn't even think about what I felt?
Awak tak fikir pun apa yang saya rasa?
Not just one.
Bukan satu sahaja.
There are many more.
Ada banyak lagi.
What's with that?
Ada apa dengan itu?
Every week, there's a new one? Huh? Damn you!
Setiap minggu, ada yang baru? Hah? sial kau!
Why can't you look at me now?
Kenapa awak tak boleh pandang saya sekarang?
Is it because it's true?
Adakah kerana ia benar?
Is it true? Tell me!
Adakah ia benar? Beritahu saya!
I gave everything to you.
Saya memberikan segalanya kepada awak.
Everything you wanted.
Semua yang anda mahukan.
Nobody else took care of you!
Tiada orang lain yang menjaga awak!
Just me!
Hanya saya!
It hurts so much.
Sakit sangat.
Mara.
serta merta.
Mara, I'm sorry.
Mara, saya minta maaf.
Say that to your other women!
Katakan itu kepada wanita anda yang lain!
Me?
saya?
I don't want this anymore.
Saya tidak mahu ini lagi.
Let's end this.
Mari kita tamatkan ini.
Damn it!
sial!
I'm so useless!
Saya sangat tidak berguna!
- Whatever. - Lea!
- Apa pun. - Lea!
Wait!
Tunggu!
Sorry.
Maaf.
Sorry. Did I wake you up?
Maaf. Adakah saya membangunkan awak?
No.
Tidak.
I don't know where I should go.
Saya tidak tahu ke mana saya harus pergi.
Why? What happened?
kenapa? Apa yang berlaku?
She's gone.
Dia sudah tiada.
She left.
Dia pergi.
I can't blame her.
Saya tidak boleh salahkan dia.
Why are you here?
Kenapa awak ada di sini?
I don't know.
saya tak tahu.
Have you ever felt like you don't belong here
Pernahkah anda merasakan anda tidak layak di sini
but you have no where else to go?
tetapi anda tidak mempunyai tempat lain untuk pergi?
Always.
Sentiasa.
I thought you love her?
Saya fikir awak cintakan dia?
I love her.
saya sayang dia.
I still love her.
Saya masih sayangkan dia.
But, it's so bland.
Tapi, hambar sangat.
I thought that's what I'm looking for.
Saya fikir itulah yang saya cari.
But, it's not.
Tetapi, tidak.
You know what?
Awak tahu tak?
You're just drunk.
Anda hanya mabuk.
I'm sober enough to know what I'm saying.
Saya cukup sedar untuk mengetahui apa yang saya katakan.
Lea, I want to forget.
Lea, aku nak lupakan.
Me too.
Saya juga.
You're leaving?
Awak nak pergi?
Yes.
ya.
Where are you going?
awak nak pergi mana?
To Batangas.
Ke Batangas.
Mara is there.
Mara ada.
I need to talk to her.
Saya perlu bercakap dengannya.
We might be able to fix this.
Kami mungkin boleh membetulkannya.
Do you think she will still accept you?
Adakah anda fikir dia masih akan menerima anda?
I don't know.
saya tak tahu.
But I need to try.
Tetapi saya perlu mencuba.
Aren't you going to say goodbye to me?
Adakah anda tidak akan mengucapkan selamat tinggal kepada saya?
What for?
untuk apa?
For me!
Bagi saya!
Lea, you can handle yourself.
Lea, awak boleh urus sendiri.
Can I really?
Bolehkah saya benar-benar?
Lea, I'm sorry.
Lea, saya minta maaf.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Saya tidak bermaksud untuk menyakiti awak.
You wanted that.
Anda mahu itu.
You just don't care.
Anda hanya tidak peduli.
Lea, you're still young.
Lea, awak masih muda.
You'll forget me eventually.
Anda akan melupakan saya akhirnya.
Do you think I want to forget you?
Awak rasa saya nak lupakan awak ke?
You need to forget me, Lea.
Awak perlu lupakan saya, Lea.
You know what? It's easy for you to say that.
Awak tahu tak? Mudah untuk awak cakap macam tu.
Because you're the one leaving me behind.
Kerana awak yang tinggalkan saya.
Lea.
Itu sahaja.
Okay.
Okay.
It's over.
dah habis.
You enjoyed it.
Anda menikmatinya.
Now, you need to leave.
Sekarang, awak perlu pergi.
You'll go back to her.
Anda akan kembali kepadanya.
What about me?
Bagaimana dengan saya?
Am I just nothing to you?
Adakah saya hanya tiada pada awak?
It's not like that, Lea.
Bukan begitu, Lea.
Then what?
Kemudian apa?
What am I?
Apa saya?
I don't know.
saya tak tahu.
I didn't plan for this.
Saya tidak merancang untuk ini.
But you wanted it, right?
Tetapi anda mahukannya, bukan?
You can't even think of a reason for me.
Anda tidak boleh memikirkan alasan untuk saya.
You shouldn't have knocked on my door that night.
Awak tak patut ketuk pintu rumah saya malam tu.
I know.
saya tahu.
But I tried, right?
Tapi saya dah cuba kan?
Because all of that means something to me, Lea.
Kerana semua itu bermakna buat saya, Lea.
Just stay here. Why do you have to leave?
Hanya tinggal di sini. Kenapa awak perlu pergi?
If I won't leave now,
Jika saya tidak akan pergi sekarang,
then I won't be able to leave at all.
maka saya tidak akan dapat pergi sama sekali.
Don't leave. Just stay here.
jangan pergi. Hanya tinggal di sini.
I can't.
saya tak boleh.
What?
apa?
Fine.
baiklah.
Leave!
Pergi!
I'm sorry.
saya minta maaf.
Bring that down. Oh, that was close!
Turunkan itu. Oh, itu sudah dekat!
You're so handsome when you lift things.
Anda sangat kacak apabila anda mengangkat barang.
Really?
Betul ke?
- Hi, neighbor. - Hello.
- Hai, jiran. - Hello.
Hello. We're the new tenants in Ramon's apartment.
Hello. Kami penyewa baru di apartmen Ramon.
Do you know him?
awak kenal dia?
Not much.
Tidak banyak.
I'm Tin.
Saya Tin.
He's Paolo, my boyfriend.
Dia Paolo, teman lelaki saya.
Lea.
Itu sahaja.
Nice to meet you. Sorry for being so loud last night.
Selamat berkenalan. Maaf kerana bising semalam.
It's okay.
tak apa.
I'm really sorry.
Saya betul-betul minta maaf.
It's nice here. It's quiet.
Di sini bagus. Ia senyap.
Yes. It's really quiet here.
ya. Sunyi sungguh di sini.
- Okay. I'll go ahead. - Sure. Nice meeting you.
- Okay. Saya akan pergi ke hadapan. - Pasti. Selamat berjumpa dengan awak.
- Come on, let's go. - Your eyes...
- Ayuh, mari kita pergi. - Mata awak...
They should only be looking at me!
Sepatutnya mereka hanya memandang saya!
Of course.
Sudah tentu.
- Oh! - Oh no!
- Oh! - Oh tidak!
- Can you do it? - Yes, I can do it.
- Bolehkah anda melakukannya? - Ya, saya boleh melakukannya.
I'll be the one to hold this.
Saya akan menjadi orang yang memegang ini.
- Can you do it? - Can I get a kiss first?
- Bolehkah anda melakukannya? - Bolehkah saya mendapatkan ciuman dahulu?
Oh!
Oh!
- Oh, you! - That was one!
- Oh, awak! - Itu adalah satu!
- Let's go! - Next time, on the lips.
- Jom pergi! - Lain kali, di bibir.
Geez!
Ya ampun!
- Geez! - Can I get another kiss?
- Ya ampun! - Bolehkah saya mendapatkan ciuman lagi?
- Come on, let's go. - Oh, you! Let's go!
- Ayuh, mari kita pergi. - Oh, awak! jom pergi!
I told you...
saya dah cakap...
Paolo!
Paul!